Finding Aid for the Michael Braver Collection of Americanist Material LSC.1585
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Reel to Reel Tapes
  - Hintzen, Walt. Riverside, CA., August 14, 1971. (Box 9)
  - Hixon, (Maj. Gen.) William V. The Plan of the Secretary of Defense. Thousand Oaks, CA., March 4, 1965. (Box 25)
  - Holmes, Lola Belle. Why I Became a Communist for the FBI. San Jose, CA., October 10, 1966. (Box 23)
  - Hollingsworth, Tom. Christian Crusade Convention. Tulsa., 1966. (Box 5, Box 23)
  - Hollingsworth. Vietnam, the No Win War. Fresno, CA., December 13, 1970. (Box 23)
  - H.O.W. (Happiness of Womanhood) Satin Pillow Rally. Los Angeles., August 26, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Hunter, (Reverend) Bud. The Tragedy of a Forsaken Inheritance. Somis, CA., February 27, 1972. (Box 5, Box 23)
  - Hurley, Patricia. Illusions About China. Oxnard, CA., March 10, 1972. (Box 7, Box 24)
  - Hutton, (Col. Ret.) (SPX Research Associates). Situation 1963., March 21, 1962. (Box 23)
  - John Birch Society Annual Council Dinner. Multiple Speakers on "The Youth of Today." Los Angeles., March 17, 1967. (Box 3, Box 25)
  - John Birch Society Annual Council Dinner 1971. Multiple Speakers on "Education." Featured speaker was Tom Anderson. Los Angeles., March 5, 1971. (Box 4)
  - John Birch Society Annual Council Dinner 1972. Featuring Robert Welch. Los Angeles., March 3, 1972. (Box 4)
  - John Birch Society Annual Council Dinner 1973. Multiple Speakers. Theme: Get U.S. Out of the United Nations. Los Angeles., March 2, 1973. (Box 4)
  - John Birch Society. Leadership Seminar. Burbank, CA., November 23, 1968. (Box 25)
  - Jordan, George Racy. Major Jordan's Diary. (On Lend Lease to Russia). Oxnard, CA., May 6, 1961. (Box 25)
  - Joseph, Raymond. Ethnic Revolution. (CACC) Anaheim, CA., February 19, 1972. (Box 10)
  - Judd, Walter M.D. 1973-1974, Crucial Years for America. Tulsa., August 4, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Judd, Walter M.D. Paris vs. Peking (CACC). Los Angeles, CA., November 11, 1960. (Box 23)
  - Judd, Walter M.D. Red China and the U.N. (CACC). Anaheim, CA., February 19, 1972. (Box 10, Box 23)
  - Kelley, Claire. (at) The Tax Rebellion Dinner. Los Angeles, CA., June 17, 1972. (Box 10)
  - Kirshner, (Dr.) Howard E. The Christian Basis of Freedom. Goleta, CA., October 16, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Kirshner. Monetary Inflation is Robbing Americans and Destroying Our Country. Buena Park, CA., September 28, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Koehl, Mathew. The National Socialist White Peoples' Party. El Monte, CA., April 7, 1973. (Box 9)
  - Lane, General Thomas. War in Vietnam. Glendale, CA., March 30, 1967. (Box 4, Box 23)
    (Americans for Constitutional Action headed by Admiral Ben Moreell).
  - Lanz, (Major) Pedro Diaz. (T.A.C.T.) Civil Turmoil from Havana to Watts. North Hollywood, CA., July 27, 1966. (Box 2, Box 24)
  - Larsen, Martin. Tax Rebellion. Los Angeles, CA., April 14, 1973. (Box 9)
  - Law, (Dr.) James. (FiPo). Meeting the Bilateral Attack. Glendale, CA., December 8, 1964. (Box 7, Box 24)
  - Lechner, John. (Americanism Educational League). An American With Guts Speaks Out, probably Los Angeles., undated, probably early 1960s.; (Pre-recorded tape). (Box 9)
  - LeMay, General Curtis. Address to UROC, Long Beach, CA., May 6, 1967. (Box 9)
  - Liberty Amendment Committee of Los Angeles County, Norwalk, CA., March 31, 1973. (Box 2)
  - Liberty Lobby. Symposium on Sex Education. Speakers included Col. Curtis Dall. John Steinbecker, Harry Von Zell, et. al. Los Angeles, CA., October 4, 1969.; (2 copies) (Box 3, 8)
  - Liberty Lobby. Tax Payers' Strike. Multiple Speakers. Los Angeles., April 15, 1972. (Box 3, 8)
  - Liberty Tea. Multiple Speakers. Long Beach, CA., April 15, 1973. (Box 4)
  - Lyon, B. TRUE News. Los Angeles., March 24, 1973. (Box 24)
  - Lyon, Bob (T.R.U.E., Tax Payers United Endeavor). Resolutions of a California Bicentennial Tea Party. Sacramento., January 8, 1973. (Box 4)
  - Lyons, Florence Fowler. UNESCO: Surrender by Treaty. At the Symposium on Freedom. Los Angeles., November 4, 1961. (Box 25)
  - McBirnie, Stuart. Why We Must Not Recognize Red China. Oakland, CA., June 14, 1966.; (2 copies) (Box 11, 23)
    General note
    (United Community Church, Glendale is McBirnie's.)
  - McBrearty, Ardie. Control is the Name of the Game. Ventura, CA., December 7, 1971. (Box 8, Box 23)
  - McCarthy, (Sen.) Joseph. Manion Forum radio broadcast #67., January 8, 1956. (Box 9, Box 25)
  - McIntire, Rev. Carl. Changing World. North Hollywood, CA., December 12, 1964. (Box 11, 24)
  - McIntire. National Council of Churches. La Crescenta, CA., May 10, 1962. (Box 11, 24)
  - McLain, Ann. Sex in the Classroom. Burbank, CA., April 12, 1969. (Box 24)
  - Maddox, (Gov.) Lester. at the John Birch Society Council Dinner. Los Angeles, CA., March 6, 1970. (Box 8, Box 24)
  - Mahaney, Pat. (T.R.A.I.N. ---JBS). Beware the Great Merger. Montague, NJ., March 18, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Mamak, Victor. Ye Shall know the Truth and the Truth shall Keep You Free. (To the Conservative Club). Thousand Oaks, CA., March 20, 1965.; (3 copies) (Box 5)
  - Manion, Dean Clarence. (Manion Forum). Our Country's Future Hangs in the Balance. (JBS Sponsored), San Francisco., April 18, 1964. (Box 7, Box 23)
  - Manion. (Manion Forum). God and the Government. San Jose, CA., October 21, 1965. (Box 24)
  - Manion. Keep God in Govt. Christian Crusade., 1961. (Box 24)
  - Manion. Survival of Western Civilization. Ventura, CA., May 28, 1963. (Box 24)
  - Manion. (Untitled). Los Angeles, CA., December 4, 1961. (Box 7, Box 24)
  - Manion, Dean Clarence. (Christian Crusade) Nine of Ten Americans are Asleep., 1960. (Box 6)
  - Marisch, Frank and Rex Westerfield. John Birch Society Leadership Seminar. Los Angeles., April 20, 1968. (Box 25)
  - Martin, Laurel. State Support for the New Morality. Encino., March 26, 1973. (Box 25)
  - Mayer, Maj. Wm. E. Brainwashing. Phoenix, AZ., January 4, 1961. (Box 25)
  - Medford, Evans. (Citizens' Council). This Country is Dying at the Top. (Racist Orientation). Jan Jose, CA., September 29, 1967. (Box 25)
  - Metlova, Maria. Black Bread and Caviar. Santa Barbara, CA., October 27, 1969. (Box 25)
  - Miller. (Rev) Lewis. (Soldiers of the Cross). Economics for Christians. Evergreen, COj., August 14, 1968. (Box 2, Box 25)
  - Miller, Marion and Paul Miller. Los Angeles, CA., January 22, 1963. (Box 25)
    (Paul was an ex-Communist, Marion a candidate for L.A. District 6 School Board).
  - Miller, Pete. (TV Newsman). Off Camera in the Media. Ventura, CA., December 2, 1972. (Box 10)
  - Millin, Leslie. Communist Takeover in China. Greater Los Angeles School of Anti-Communism., November 10, 1960. (Box 1, Box 24)
  - Moore, Rev. George and Reynolds, Rev. M.H. Rally Against Russian Churchmen. Encino, CA., February 22, 1963. (Box 10, 24)
  - Morris, Robert. (CACC). Pattern for Subversion. Los Angeles., November 11, 1960. (Box 1, Box 23)
  - Morris. No Wonder We are Losing. (CACC) Los Angeles., November 10, 1960. (Box 10, Box 23)
  - Noebel, Reverend David. (Christian Crusade). Communism, Hypnotism, and the Beatles. Santa Barbara, CA., January 16, 1965.; (3 copies) (Box 2, 9, Box 23, 25)
    - Communism, Hypnotism and the Beatles, 1965 January 16; yrlsc_1585_002_002; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:44:42) 7 inches (Box 2, Case 2)
      Transcribed from container: Rev. David Noebel of Christian Crusade tells about the Commnist use of music to subvert and control students from kindergarten through college. Meeting was held on January 16, 1965 in Santa Barbara, California
  - Noebel, Reverend David. (Christian Crusade). Communism, Hypnotism, and the Beatles. Ventura, CA., April 1, 1965. (Box 5)
  - Noebel. (CC) The Beatles: Drugs, Sex and Revolution, Long Beach, CA., March 15, 1970 (Box 4, Box 23)
  - Noebel. Communism and Christianity. Tulsa., August 5, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Noebel. The Erosion of American's National Purpose. Tulsa., August 4, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Noebel. The Marxist Minstrels. Tulsa., August 5, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Noebel. Modern Man in Rebellion Against God. Tulsa., August 4, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Noebel. Rhythm, Riots, and Revolution. El Segundo, CA., May 22, 1966. (Box 6, Box 23)
  - Norman, Jose. Cuba, Castro, and Communism. North Hollywood, CA., March 5, 1965. (Box 4, Box 23)
    (Also called, "Is Cuba Being Betrayed Again?")
  - Norman. Cuba Today, Los Angeles., March 25, 1962. (Box 7, Box 24)
  - O'Campo, Melchoir. Caesar Chavez--Another Facet of the Total Communist Conspiracy. (TACT Committee---JBS Affiliated). Bakersfield, CA, October 14, 1971. (Box 10, Box 25)
  - Oliver, Revilo P. (JBS). Marxmanship in Dallas. Glendale, CA., August 27, 1964. (Box 4, Box 24, 25)
  - Otepka, Otto. The Ordeal. Santa Monica, CA., November 14, 1972. (Box 25)
  - Passow, James. Urban Renewal and Land Reform Grab. Los Angeles, CA., August 3, 1962. (Box 23)
  - Patrick, Wm. Penn. Jake Spatz for Assemblyman. Simi, CA., October 29, 1966. (Box 23, 25)
  - Patterson, Leonard. (Paterson is a Black member of the JBS who used to be a Communist Party Member). A Report on Civil Rights. Thousand Oaks, CA., September 23, 1965. (Box 5, Box 23)
  - Patterson, L. (T.A.C.T.) My Moscow Training in Civil Rights. Santa Monica, CA., January 31, 1966. (Box 3, Box 23)
  - Palmer, Johnson. (Spokesman re the "Anti-Communist" Bible Presbyterian Church, Hollywood, CA., 1963. (Box 3)
  - Pearson, Larry. Support Your Local Police. Canoga Park, CA., March 25, 1969. (Box 23)
  - Pedigo, Jess (Dr.). Satan Worship. Sign of the Times. Tulsa., August 4, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Penabaz, (Dr.) Fernando. (Christian Crusade). The Soviet Union's New Methods for World Conquest. El Segundo, CA., May 21, 1966. (Box 9, Box 23)
  - Penebaz, F. How Castro Operates Within the USA. El Segundo, CA., October 15, 1966. (Box 9, Box 23)
  - Penebaz. (Christian Crusade). What is Communism. Ventura. CA., October 15, 1966.; (2 copies). (Box 10, Box 23, 25)
  - Phillips, (Mrs.) Emily. (former PTA Pres.) (Sponsored by The Conservative Club) Liberal Control and Subversive Activity by the PTA. Thousand Oaks, CA., January 7, 1965.; (2 copies) (Box 9)
  - Philbrick, Herbert. [The] Assassination of President Kennedy. Berkeley, CA., February 3, 1965.; (2 copies) (Box 8, Box 9)
  - Philbrick, Herbert. Cybernetic Warfare. (CACC). Los Angeles., November 9, 1960. (Box 10, Box 24)
  - Philprick, Herbert. Zero Hour for America. Ventura, CA., March 27, 1962. (Box 10, Box 25)
  - Poling, Daniel. The National Council of Churches. Phoenix., July 18, 1962. (Box 7, Box 23)
  - Poling, (Dr.) Daniel. What the Flag is Saying. Los Angeles., December 12, 1961 (Box 8, Box 23)
    (See Project Alert).
  - Poacher, Wayne. Life Line. Radio Broadcasts on KBLA from WA. O.C., 1962. (Box 8)
  - Project Alert (organized by Cleon Skousen). Los Angeles, CA., December 12, 1961. (Box 8)
  - Prussian, Karl. Communism in California. Pleasant Valley, CA., September 30, 1961. (Box 23)
  - Prussian, Karl. Inside a Communist Cell. Location and date unknown. (Box 7)
  - Prussian, Karl. Untitled. Thousand Oaks, CA., September 14, 1964. (Box 23)
  - Rassmussen, (Rev.) Roland, Why Bishop Pike Should Not have been Acquitted of Heresy Three Times. Canoga Park, CA., February 13, 1966.; (2 copies) (Box 7, 8, Box 23)
  - Richardson, (CA St. Senator) Bill. Speech, UROC Quarterly Conf. Ventura, CA., February 13, 1966.; (2 copies). (Box 1, 10)
  - Rickenbacker, (Capt.) Edward V. (Freedom Club). New Frontiers Without Freedom. Los Angeles., December 10, 1963. (Box 9, Box 23)
  - Rice, Charles. Constitutional Issues Involved in Anti-Subversive Legislation (CACC). Anaheim, CA., February 19, 1972; (2 copies). (Box 10, Box 23)
  - Roberts, (Maj.) Arch E. Why Your Son Serves Under the U.N. Command of an Enemy Soviet. (Christian Crusade). Santa Barbara, CA., January 16, 1965. (Box 5, Box 23)
  - Roberts. The United Nations (CC)., July 1964. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Rousselot, Rep. John. (John Birch Society). Disarmament--Blue Print for Surrender. Ventura, CA., April 9, 1963. (Box 3, Box 24)
  - Rousselot. Disarmament, Burbank, CA., March 8, 1963. (Box 2, Box 24)
  - Rousselot. Does Private Enterprise have an Interest in the John Birch Society? San Francisco., January 16, 1968. (Box 8)
  - Rousselot. Rep. John. The Organized Drive Against Anti-Communism. JBS l5th Symposium on Freedom. Hollywood, CA., September 2, 1961. (Box 5, Box 24)
  - Rousselot. The United Nations. San Francisco., June 22, 1965. (Box 24)
  - Rowe, H. Edward. Christian Discernment. Van Nuys, CA., September 20, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Rushdoony, (Rev.) Roussas. Christianity and the Ecology Issue. Buena Park, CA., October 19, 1973. (Box 24)
  - Rushdoony. Christian Social Ethics. Burbank, CA., October 23, 1965.; (2 copies). (Box 24)
  - Rushdoony. The Education Issue: What Is Public Education doing to America. Buena Park, CA., October 5, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Rushdoony, (Rev.) Roussas. Liberty and Property. Menlo Park, CA., October 26, 1965. (Box 7, Box 23)
  - Rushdoony. Major Trends Today from a Christian Perspective. Buena Park, CA., September 21, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Rushdoony. [The] Meaning of Life and Death--Perspective on Capital Punishment. [Moral Advance Meeting]. Anaheim, CA., September 12, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Rushdoony. Money and Progress. Sunnyvale, CA., January 16, 1968. (Box 8, Box 24)
  - Rushdoony. Possibilities of De-Population. Sunnyvale, CA., May 14, 1968. (Box 8, Box 23)
  - Schmitz, (Sen.) John. The American Opinion Bookstore Fundraiser. (JBS) Norwalk, CA., October 18, 1966. (Box 10, Box 25)
  - Schmitz. A U.S. Congressman Speaks Out. Downey, CA., February 25, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Schwartz. Cause, Course and Cure of Communism. (CACC) Los Angeles, November 9, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Schwartz Cause, Course and Cure of Communism, 1960 November 9; yrlsc_1585_004_001a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:27:49) 7 inches (Box 4, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: A. Cause, Course, and Cure of Communism; by Dr. Fred Schwarz
    - Schwartz Cause, Course and Cure of Communism, 1960 November 10; yrlsc_1585_004_001b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:08) 7 inches (Box 4, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: B. Communist Party, Fronts, and Captive Organization by Dr. Fred Schwarz
  - Schuartz. Cause and Course of Communism. Los Angeles., November 29, 1960. (Box 1)
  - Schuartz, Fred. Communist Appeal to the Intellectual. (CACC) Los Angeles., August 28, 1961. (Box 5)
  - Schukardt, Francis. (Regional Lay Director of the Blue Army). Peace Plan From Heaven. Sierra Vista, AZ., February 19, 1964. (Box 25)
  - Schwartz, Fred. (Christian Anti-Communist Crusade). Anarchism. Palo Alto, CA., February 19, 1973. (Box 24)
  - Schwartz. Cause, Course and Cure of Communism. (CACC) Los Angeles., November 9, 1960. (Box 23)
  - Schwartz. Cause and Course of Communism. Los Angeles., November 29, 1960. (Box 24)
  - Schwartz. The Communist Party. Los Angeles., November 9, 1960. (Box 3)
  - Schwartz. Communist Party, Fronts, Organizations. (CACC) Los Angeles., November 10, 1960. (Box 4, Box 23, 24)
  - Schwartz. Communist Philosophy and Method of Violence. Los Angeles., November 9, 1960. (Box 3, Box 23)
    (Also titled, Communist Theory and Practice of Violence)
  - Schwartz. Communist Program for World Conquest. (CACC). Phoenix., March 2, 1961. (Box 23)
  - Schwartz. Debating a Communist, (CACC) Los Angeles., November 11, 1960. (Box 1, Box 23)
  - Schwartz. Dialectical Materialism. (CACC)., August 29, 1962. (Box 1, Box 23)
  - Schwartz. How to Debate with Communists. (CACC) Los Angeles., September 1, 1961. (Box 23)
  - Schwartz. Leninism. Palo Alto, CA., February 17, 1973. (Box 24)
  - Schwartz. Lessons of the Cuban Crisis. Los Angeles., November 23, 1962.; (2 copies). (Box 9)
  - Schwartz. Marcuse and the Politics of Sex., February 19, 1973. (Box 24)
  - Schwartz. Philosophy of Communism. Los Angeles., November 7, 1960. (Box 2)
    - Schwartz Philosophy of Communisim, 1960 November 7; yrlsc_1585_002_001a; Schwarz, Fried, 1913-2009; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:11:36) 7 inches (Box 2, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: 1-A Philosophy of Communism- Swartz; 1-B Why Millionaires, Professors, and Ministers Become Communists- Swartz; 2-A Is Communism Constitutional?- Fred Schlaly (?); 2B- Communism and Eduction- Cleon Skousen; Afternoon Session.
    - Schwartz Philosophy of Communisim, 1960 November 7; yrlsc_1585_002_001b; Schwarz, Fried, 1913-2009; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:37) 7 inches (Box 2, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: 1-A Philosophy of Communism- Swartz; 1-B WHy Millionaires, Professors, and Ministers Become Communists- Swartz; 2-A Is Communism Constitutional?- Fred Schlaly (?); 2B- Communism and Eduction- Cleon Skousen; Afternoon Session.
  - Schwartz. Philosophy of Communism. Los Angeles., August 28, 1961.; (2 copies) (Box 3, 4, Box 24)
  - Schwartz. Marxism. Palo Alto, CA., February 17, 1973. (Box 24)
  - Schwartz. The Treatment of Communism. (CACC). Los Angeles., November 10, 1960. (Box 10, Box 23)
  - Schwartz. Why Millionaires, Professors, and Ministers become Communists, Los Angeles., November 7, 1960. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Schlafly, Fred. Is Communism Constitutional. (CACC) Los Angeles., November 7, 1960. (Box 2)
  - Seagraves, Kelly. The Search for Noah's Ark. La Mirada, CA., October 22, 1971. (Box 25)
  - Secrest, (Rev) Charles. (CC), Sex Education. Long Beach, CA., March 15, 1970. (Box 4, Box 23)
  - Skousen, Cleon. The Attack on Law and Law Enforcement. San Jose, CA., December 6, 1965. (Box 1)
  - Skousen, Cleon. Communism and Education. (CACC). Los Angeles., November 7, 1960. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Skousen. Communist Psychiatry and Crime. Los Angeles., November 8, 1960.; (2 copies). (Box 2, 4, Box 24)
  - Skousen. The Liberty Amendment. Norwalk, CA., March 31, 1973. (Box 2, 4)
  - Skousen. Those Naked Capitalists. Pasadena, CA., February 16, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Skousen. The Naked Communist. (CACC) Los Angeles., August 28, 1960. (Box 1, Box 24)
  - Skousen, Cleon. The Secret Weapon of Communism. (CACC), Los Angeles., September 1, 1961. (Box 8, Box 23)
  - Skousen. The Soft Team vs the Firm Team, "The Valley Forum" at San Jose, CA., November 8, 1963. (Box 6, Box 25)
  - Sluis, Joost et. al. Design for Victory, Greater Los Angeles School of AntiCommunism., November 9-11, 1960. (Box 1)
  - Sluis, Joost. Communist Economic Warfare. Los Angeles., November 10, 1960. (Box 1, 10, Box 23)
  - Sluis. Communism in South America. (CACC) Los Angeles., November 9, 1960. (Box 1, 10, Box 23)
  - Sluis, (Dr.) Juis, F. Schwartz, and B. Strube. Design for Victory. (CACC). Los Angeles., November 9, 1960.; (2 copies). (Box 10, Box 24)
  - Smith, Charles. Civil Rights--A Fraud. Arcadia, CA., May 19, 1970. (Box 24)
  - Smitherman, Joel. (Mayor of Selma, AL.). Interview., 1963. (Box 11)
  - Smoot, Dan. Robert Qelch Testimonial. Hollywood, CA., October 11, 1965.; (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Stang, Alan. Excursions into Chaos: Forced Busing. San Diego., February 21, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Stang, Alan. What is Wrong with our Schools. Houston., June, 1970. (Box 24)
  - Stang, Alan. The Making of Revolutionaries: where our schools went wrong. Mahopac, NY., April 22, 1971.; (2 copies) (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Stang. (Nix-on OSHA Committee). Bad Business. Newburgh, NY., June 15, 1973. (Box 24)
  - Stanley, Scott Jr. (JBS). Red Heads of State. Berkeley, CA., June 6, 1968.; (2 copies) (Box 1, Box 23, 25)
  - Stanley, S. Red Heads of State, Santa Clara, CA., February 24, 1965. (Box 1, Box 25)
  - Stark, (Sgt.) Peter (T.A.C.T.-~JBS) Vietnam Sellout. Burbank, CA., January 25, 1969. (Box 3, Box 24)
  - Steinbacher, John. [The] Dilemma in Education: the Ravages of Secular Humanism. [Moral Advance Action Forum]. Anaheim, CA., November 14, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Steinbacher, John. Ideological, Philosophical, and Religious Change in America. Ventura, CA., December 14, 1971. (Box 24)
  - Steinbacher, J. and Eleanor Howe. The Conceptual Revolution. Corona Del Mar, CA., January 27, 1973. (Box 23)
  - Stone, Willis E. (National Committee for Economic Freedom). The Personal Income Tax and Why It Is Not Necessary. Santa Barbara, CA., July 27, 1962. (Box 24)
  - Stone. The Liberty Amendment. Norwalk, CA., March 31, 1973. (Box 3)
  - Stone. The Liberty Amendment. See We the People. Phoenix, October 24, 1970. (Box 3)
  - Stone. Put out the Fire. (T.R.U.E.) Sacramento, CA, January 8, 1973. (Box 3)
  - Strube, Wm. (VP, CACC). A Program for Action, Greater L.A. School of AntiCommunism., November 11, 1960. (Box 5, Box 24)
  - Stump, Felix. Communism Inside and Outside USA. Los Angeles., December 12, 1961. (Box 8, Box 23)
    (see Project Alert).
  - Sullivan, Thom. Mental Health Racket. Los Angeles. Sullivan. Mental Health Racket. Los Angeles, September 1, 1961. November 16, 1961.; [one tape] (Box 9)
  - Sullivan. Mental Health Racket. Los Angeles., March 22, 1962. (Box 9)
  - Tax Rebellion Committee of Los Angeles County. Taxpayer's strike. Multiple Speakers. Los Angeles., April 15, 1972. (Box 5)
  - Taylor, James R. (Committee of Christian Laymen). The National Council of Churches Uses Their Influence to Support Communist Aims., undated. (Box 5)
    See We the People, Phoenix.
  - Terry, Paul. (Copley News, San Diego). Press Freedom and Responsibility. Los Angeles., November 10, 1960. (Box 1, Box 23)
  - Troxell, Dick. The Federal Reserve System. Shreveport., April 14, 1966. (Box 9, Box 23)
  - T.R.U.E. (Tax Reformers United Endeavor) Tax Tea Party and Seminar., undated. (Box 5)
    Various Speakers including Bob Lyon, John Steinbacher, Anita Kerns, Jim Townsend, A.J. Porth, Floyd Wakefield, Willis Stone, Glenn Bernd, and John Rakus.
  - UROC (United Republicans of California) Convention, In Long Beach, CA., undated. (Box 1)
    Including speakers sometimes associated with far right causes. Patty Newman ("Pass the Poverty Please"), Harry Tridinoff ("The White Russian"). Gordon Browning (once affiliated with FIPO), Bill Richardson, the CA State Senator affiliated with the Birch Society.
  - UROC. St. Convention. Debate/Polling for Ashbrook vs Nixon. San Jose, CA., May 7, 1972. (Box 9, 6, 8)
  - Van Impe, (Dr.) Jack. Coming War with Russia, Bellflower, CA., February 22, 1972. (Box 10, Box 25)
  - Wakefield, Floyd. The Liberty Amendment. Norwalk, CA., March 31, 1973. (Box 10)
  - Wald, Margaret. Roles of Women Under Communism, Los Angeles., November 10, 1960. (Box 1, Box 23)
  - Walker, General Edwin. Operation Midnight Ride {CC), Greenville, South Carolina., March 12, 1963. (Box 6, Box 23)
  - Wallace, (Former Gov.) George. Untitled. San Francisco., October 30, 1967. (Box 10, 25)
  - Wallace, (Former Gov.) George. Untitled. Santa Barbara, CA., December 11, 1967. (Box 10, 25)
  - Ward, Chester. Communism Inside and Outside the USA. (Project Alert), December 12, 1961. (Box 8, Box 23)
  - Ward. National Suicide by International Agreement (CACC)., August 28, 1961. (Box 3, Box 24)
  - We the People. All American Conference, Phoenix., August 28, 1961. (Box 3)
  - Wells, Dr. Protect Alert. Los Angeles., December 12, 1961. (Box 3)
  - Weniger, G.A. Dress Rehearsal for Revolution. Christian Crusade., 1961. (Box 23)
  - Weniger, G.A. Operation Abolition of Education. (CC). Los Angeles, 1963. (Box 8)
  - Welch, Robert. (John Birch Society). A Blue Book on Tape, Berkeley, CA., May 23, 1964 May 24, 1964; (2 copies) (Box 4, 7)
  - Welch, Robert. (John Birch Society). If I Were President. Los Angeles, CA., March 1, 1968; (2 copies). (Box 3, 9, Box 24)
    - If I Were President, 1968 March 1; yrlsc_1585_002_003a; Welch, Robert, 1899-1985; John Birch Society; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:43:32) 7 inches (Box 3, Case 1)